https://www.allacademic.com/privacy

All Academic Privacy Policy
We take your right to privacy seriously and want you to feel confident using our software. This Privacy Policy deals with All Academic’s use of personally identifiable information that may be collected by us on one of our sites. This Policy does not apply to other entities that we do not own or control, or persons that are not our employees, agents, or within our control.
Data Collection
We do not collect personal information about you unless you specifically and knowingly provide such information to us. Any information collected is used only by All Academic for the purposes stated at the time of collection or as otherwise set out in this privacy statement. All Academic collects and uses your information only for the following purposes:
To respond to requests for further information about our products.
To provide All Academic’s partners with support.
To support operational processes within All Academic’s software, such as conference submission and review.
For research purposes defined by All Academic’s clients (data controllers).
To meet legal and regulatory requirements.
We endeavor to only collect the personal information necessary in these circumstances. Personal information collected may include your name, address, phone number, fax number, institutional affiliation, and e-mail address. All personal information collected from the public All Academic website is stored in our secure database. Only authorized All Academic employees and authorized administrators of the specific site have access to this information.
Most of the All Academic websites require use of a username and password for access. This username and password allows you to access certain areas such as submission, review and management portions of a site.
Use of Data.
We will ensure that your Data is not to be provided to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party, by way of example an Application Service Provider; (iv) pursuant to legal process or law enforcement; (v) we find that your use of this site violates our Policy, Terms of Service, other usage guidelines or as deemed reasonably necessary by us to protect our legal rights and/or property; In the event you choose to use links that appear on our site to visit other platforms, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites.
Cookies
All Academic may use a technology called ‘cookies’ to record or track information related to visitors to our public website. Cookies are simple text files that web browsers place on computer hard drives when sites are visited. These cookies are specific to the website session and are not used to record personal information or to associate personal information with the use of the All Academic service. The All Academic application utilizes session specific cookies so that only authenticated users can navigate the application, and to provide extra security to prevent session hijacking.
In order to improve access to content based on visitors' browsers and operating system types, and to make our content available to as many visitors as possible, All Academic may collect certain technical information from your computer’s web browser or Internet device when you visit a site in the allacademic.com domain. This information includes the amount of time spent on the site by a visitor with a unique Internet identifier, the pages visited and returned to, the operating system, and Web browser used, the referring Web site and any keywords used to find our site on a search website. These server logs may also be used to track bugs, and to provide support to users. Browsing history, and personal information is not shared with any third party, and is not used for marketing purposes.
Third-Party Sites
We will ensure that your Data is not to be provided to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party, by way of example an Application Service Provider; (iv) a service is a key component of a client’s conference (e.g. a mobile app or an archive);(v) pursuant to legal process or law enforcement; (vi) we find that your use of this site violates our Policy, Terms of Service, other usage guidelines or as deemed reasonably necessary by us to protect our legal rights and/or property.
The All Academic websites may contain links to other websites. All Academic is not responsible for the privacy policies of, or the content of these websites. Website visitors and customers need to read the privacy statements of other websites to understand their privacy policies.
Papers archived on All Academic’s Research site may include Google Ads. These ads may include cookies that are not controlled, stored, or used by All Academic. Please visit Google to see their privacy policy.
Payment Processors
We rarely process payments, but if we do, we will use third parties to process payments made through the All Academic website and the services that we may make available to you. If you choose to make a purchase through our website or such services, please note that we will direct you to a third party for the processing of such payments.
Collected Information
User names and email addresses ("User Information") are collected and maintained in the All Academic application for purposes of managing the login authentication process, and to allow the application to send notifications to the end user. An example of an application notification would be an email notice informing the user that a submission has been accepted or rejected.
All Academic will not give any User Information to a third party, unless we are required to do so in order to comply with the law.
Institutional affiliations, areas of expertise and other fields collected during the sign-up period for a conference website or other website hosted by All Academic (“Profile Information”) are collected for the purposes of submitting one’s work to a conference, to facilitate the assignment of reviews, and to link a person to their scholarly work. All Academic works to minimize the amount of Profile Information displayed to the public to fields necessary to give submitters credit for their scholarly work. This information is distributed to third parties only for the purposes of displaying information necessary for the running of a conference such as conference programs, schedules, and archives.
All Academic may provide minimal profile information to a third party for the purpose of a conference mobile app, archiving, or other purposes requested by All Academic’s clients (the data controller).
Changes to Personal Information
Our software is configured to enable you to access end-users’ personal information, and to correct or delete it if requested. In most cases, users can access their own personal data to make corrections – unless the data controller (client) have prevented them from doing so (e.g. during the review process, during scheduling, or after a site has been archived).
Hosting Privacy Policy
For current customers of the All Academic software service, we are committed to protecting your privacy. One of the ways in which we demonstrate this commitment is through the care we take to protect the privacy of information which we collect when we host your data on our servers. All Academic's servers are hosted in a secure, state of the art data center that is fully equipped with a comprehensive set of safety and security systems that guard against any conceivable threat, including fire, earthquake, physical and virtual attacks. All data center systems, including power management, environmental, and network architecture, are equipped with backup systems.
Security Measures
• Continuous deployment of proven, up-to-date security technologies and best practices.
• Ongoing evaluation of emerging security developments and threats.
• Commitment to a secure, scalable, hosted system.
• Security redundancy throughout the All Academic architecture.
Physical Security
Production equipment is located in a secure facility which provides 24-hour physical security, and video monitoring. Redundant electrical generators, data center chillers and other back-up equipment designed to keep servers up and running are continuously monitored.
Data Encryption
All Academic uses 128-bit SSL for secure HTTP connections between client computers and our servers.
User Authentication
Users access All Academic client websites only with a valid username and password combination, which is encrypted via SSL while in transmission.
Operating System Security
All Academic enforces tight operating system-level security by using a minimal number of entry points to all production servers. All systems are hardened and protected with strong passwords, and maintained at each vendor’s recommended patch level.
Changes to Privacy Policy
All Academic may make changes to this Policy from time to time. Changes will be posted on this webpage.
